(Amy:)What does your card say, Bernadette?
(Leonard:)Hang on. Do you think
we'd really drift apart
(Leonard:)if we both became successful?
(Penny:)Of course not.
(Penny:)If I became a famous actress
and had to move,
(Penny:)you would just come with me.
(Leonard:)But if I get a chance
to be a tenured professor,
(Leonard:)I might not have that much
choice in where I end up.
(Penny:)Yeah, but if I become
a successful actress,
(Penny:)we wouldn't need the money.
(Leonard:)Well, you don't go
into science for the money.
(Bernadette:)Speak for yourself.
(Bernadette:)Last month, my company both invented
and cured Restless Eye Syndrome.
(Bernadette:)Ka-Ching, ya blinky chumps.
(Penny:)So, wait, if my career
took me somewhere else,
(Penny:)you might not go?
I (VOCALIZES DRAMATIC MUSIC)
(Amy:)He started it.
(Raj:)Okay, guys, new back stories.
(Raj:)Penny and Leonard, you two lovebirds
(Raj:)are super successful
and living in New York.
(Raj:)You're an actress, you're a professor
and you have three beautiful kids.